Is that Estermont?
Tarth, Ser Jaime.
The Sapphire Isle.
Why are we on a merchant ship?
Why no Lannister sails?
This ship's sailing to Oldtown.
We'll get off earlier
not far from Sunspear,
row ourselves to the Dornish
shore in the night.
You ever been to Dorne?
- No.
- I have.
The Dornish are crazy.
All they want to do is fight
and fuck, fuck and fight.
You should be happy to go back.
There's nothing
like a good fight
to get you in the mood
for fucking.
And there's nothing like
a fuck-mad Dornish girl
to clear your head
for the next fight.
It's how the two work together.
Now we're gonna be doing
a lot of fighting, I'm sure.
Well, I am.
But I don't imagine we'll get
to stick around for the rest.
Not after we've kidnapped
their princess.
We're not kidnapping
We're rescuing my niece,
bringing her back to her family.
Your niece?
I've been doing this sort
of thing a long time.
- I'm good at it.
- That's why you're here.
I know. Why are you here?
Why not send 40 of me?
Or an army?
Unlike most folks,
you've actually got one.
Because I don't want
to start a war.
That still doesn't explain
what you're doing here.
It has to be me.
If I'm putting something
like this together,
a one-handed man
who happens to be
one of the most recognizable
faces in Westeros is not...
It has to be me.
You set your brother
free, didn't you?
I'll bet your sister
didn't like that.
Varys set him free.
Well, if you ever see
the wee fucker,
give him my regards.
He murdered my father.
If I ever see him,
I'll split him in two.
And then I'll give
him your regards.
The Iron Bank has called in
one-tenth of the crown's debts.
Given the expense of
rebuilding the royal fleet...
How much can the crown afford?
With winter coming,
half what they ask, less?
You're the Master of Coin.
How do we pay them?
House Tyrell could
front the gold
and the crown would
pay us back in time
or I'd have words
with my daughter.
You've already
given us too much.
No, we must arrange better
terms with the Iron Bank.
- Absolutely.
- In person.
- Me?
- We must send an envoy to the Iron Bank,
someone of importance to show
these bankers our respect.
As the king's Master of Coin, I can
think of no one more qualified.
I would be honored, Your Grace.
The king's expressed concern about his
father-in-law's safety on this voyage.
He's ordered Ser Meryn to
personally lead your escort.
My very own Kingsguard?
- Please express my...
- Safe travels, Lord Tyrell.
Of course. Of course.
I'll give your regards
to the Titan of Braavos.
( laughs )
The small council grows
smaller and smaller.
Not small enough.
Cersei: May I offer you
some wine, Your Holiness?
No.
The old High Septon would
have asked the vintage.
I could say that our minds
are temples to the Seven
and should be kept pure.
But the truth is
I don't like the taste.
Hmm.
How may I serve?
All over Westeros we hear
of septs being burned,
Silent Sisters raped,
bodies of holy men
piled in the streets.
Wars teach people to obey
the sword, not the gods.
Perhaps the gods
need a sword of their own.
In the days before
the Targaryens,
the Faith Militant dispensed
the justice of the Seven.
Well, the Faith Militant was disarmed
more than two centuries ago.
If I explain their holy
purpose to my son the king,
I have no doubt
he will sign a decree
arming the believers
you felt worthy.
An army that defends the bodies
and souls of the common people?
An army in service
to the gods themselves.
And to you, of course,
as the chosen representative
of the Seven.
An honor I never expected.
Or, indeed, ever wished for.
Which is why you were chosen.
You and I both know
how the world works.
Too often the wicked
are the wealthiest,
beyond the reach of justice.
The king himself cannot always
punish those who deserve it most.
All sinners are equal
before the gods.
What would you say if I told you of
a great sinner in our very midst?
Shielded by gold and privilege.
May the Father judge him justly.
( Merchants shouting )
( grunts )
( people screaming )
( muffled groaning )
- ( grunting )
- What are you doing?
( Man grunts )
Help me! Help me!
- ( Moans )
- Yeah. Yeah.
( Screams ) Get off me!
( Grunts )
- Come on.
- ( women shriek )
Shut up! Move!
( Women screaming )
This is Lord Petyr
Baelish's establishment.
( Grunts )
( man screams )
Faith Militant: Cocksuckers.
Boy fucker.
You buggering filth!
There's a special place in the
seventh hell for your kind.
Man: Please. Please, I'll pay.
I'll... I'll pay all of you.
Yes, you will.
( Man screams )
( panting )
( grunting )
( applause )
Seize him.
- Sinner.
- ( grunting )
Loras: Get your hands off me.
Ser Loras of House Tyrell,
you have broken the laws
of gods and men.
Who do you think you are?
Justice.
Why is my brother in a cell?
I-I don't know.
I-I didn't order it.
We both know who did.
You told me she was
returning to Casterly Rock.
Are you saying
my mother's behind this?
She's jealous
you're not hers anymore.
Arresting my brother
is her revenge.
Aren't you and Mother
getting along?
( Huffs )
Oh, my sweet, sweet king.
Do you have any affection
for me at all?
Of course I do.
You're my queen.
I can't bear
to think of my brother
locked away in some grimy cell.
I'll set him free for you.
Do you promise?
I demand that
Ser Loras be freed now.
Did I arrest him?
Well, no.
But y-you armed
the Faith Militant.
You gave the High Sparrow
an army.
I did.
And your wife has
every right to criticize.
We can't allow fanatics
to arrest the queen's brother
no matter his perversions.
Then...
can I tell Margaery you'll
have Ser Loras released?
I told you,
I'm not holding Ser Loras.
You're the king.
I'm sure if you speak
to the High Sparrow,
he'll release the poor boy.
Halt!
( Coughing, chatter )
His Holiness is praying.
He will not be disturbed.
Give the order and we'll
clear out this rabble.
You mean, kill them?
Here at the sept?
You'd be sending them to meet
the gods that they love.
Man: Bastard!
Man ♪2: You're an abomination!
Man ♪3: Born of sin!
Woman: Filthy bastard!
We'll find another way.
Man ♪4: Abomination!
My queen?
There was no way to free Ser
Loras without violence.
You're the King of the Andals,
the Lord of the Seven Kingdoms,
the Protector of the Realm,
and you let a band of fanatics
imprison your brother by law.
I'm going to speak
with the High Sparrow.
Are you? When?
- I-I don't know.
- You don't know?
He was praying just now.
I have to send word
to Grandmother.
Will you come back later?
I need to be with
my family, Your Grace.
Of course.
( Grunting )
Selyse: You think
highly of this boy?
Good.
Stannis: Lord Commander
of the Night's Watch.
And a bastard
by some tavern slut.
Perhaps, but that
wasn't Ned Stark's way.
I should have given you a son.
Not your fault.
Whose, then?
I gave you nothing but weakness.
And deformity.
Those scars mean nothing
to the Lord of Light.
My lady.
Her father is the Lord's
chosen king,
and her father's blood
runs through her veins.
You march on Winterfell soon?
We must to beat the snows.
Once before, you put
your faith in Ser Davos
and left me behind.
I hope you won't make
that mistake again.
I won't.
I need you.
You only need faith, my king.
And you, my lady,
what do you need?
To serve my Lord.
( Grunting )
Lord Ashford.
Lady Caulfield.
Oh, Lord Smallwood.
I've never even heard
of these people.
They haven't heard
of you, either.
But we need men
and they have some.
How many men does this
Lord Mayzen have to send us?
More than Lord Wibberley.
- Not him.
-  I know, I'm sorry.
But we need men and supplies
and Roose Bolton's
the Warden of the North.
He murdered my brother.
We swore to be
the watchers on the Wall.
We can't watch the Wall
with 50 men.
And we can't get more men
without help from
the Warden of the North.
Apologies, my lady.
( Door closes )
Lord Commander.
How can I help you?
Come with us when we ride south.
None of us know the
castle as well as you do.
Its hidden tunnels,
its weaknesses,
its people.
Winterfell was your home once.
Don't you want to chase
the rats out of it?
Castle Black is my home now.
The Night's Watch take no part in
the wars of the Seven Kingdoms.
There's only one war.
Life against death.
Come, let me show you
what you're fighting for.
You're gonna show me
some vision in the fire?
Forgive me, my lady,
I don't trust in visions.
No visions. No magic.
Just life.
Do you feel my heart beating?
There's power in you.
You resist it,
and that's your mistake.
Embrace it.
The Lord of Light
made us male and female.
Two parts of a greater whole.
In our joining, there's power.
Power to make life,
power to make light,
and power to cast shadows.
I don't think Stannis
would like that very much.
Then we shouldn't tell him.
- I can't.
- Why?
I swore a vow.
I loved another.
The dead don't need lovers.
Only the living.
I know.
But I still love her.
You know nothing, Jon Snow.
( Knocks on door )
Are you lonely?
Just bored.
My father used
to tell me that boredom
indicates a lack
of inner resources.
Were you bored a lot, too?
I know Castle Black
is no place for a child, but...
I like it. I thought
I'd be left at home.
I know Mother
didn't want to bring me.
Why do you say that?
She told me, "I don't
want to bring you."
She shouldn't have said that.
Are you ashamed of me, Father?
When you were an infant,
a Dornish trader
landed on Dragonstone.
His goods were junk
except for one wooden doll.
He had even sewn a dress on it
in the colors of our house.
No doubt he had
heard of your birth
and assumed new fathers
were easy targets.
I still remember how you smiled when
I put that doll in your cradle.
How you pressed it
to your cheek.
By the time we burned the
doll, it was too late.
I was told you would die.
Or worse,
the greyscale would go slow.
Let you grow just enough
to know the world
before taking it away from you.
Everyone advised me to send
you to the ruins of Valyria
to live out your short life
with the Stone Men
before the sickness
spread through the castle.
I told them all to go to hell.
I called in every maester
on this side of the world.
Every healer. Every apothecary.
They stopped the disease
and saved your life.
'Cause you did not belong
across the world
with the bloody Stone Men.
You are the Princess Shireen
of House Baratheon.
And you are my daughter.
( Water dripping )
Littlefinger: I thought
I might find you here.
Your Aunt Lyanna.
Father never talked about her.
Sometimes I'd find him down
here lighting the candles.
They say she was beautiful.
I saw her once.
I was a boy living
with your mother's family.
Lord Whent held a great
tourney at Harrenhal.
Everyone was there.
The Mad King, your father,
Robert Baratheon,
and Lyanna.
She was already
promised to Robert.
You can imagine
what it was like for me,
a boy from nowhere
with nothing to his name,
watching these legendary men
tilting at the lists.
The last two riders
were Barristan Selmy
and Rhaegar Targaryen.
When Rhaegar won, everyone
cheered for their prince.
I remember the girls laughing
when he took off his helmet
and they saw that silver hair.
How handsome he was.
Until he rode
right past his wife,
Elia Martell,
and all the smiles died.
I've never seen
so many people so quiet.
He rode past his wife
and he lay a crown of winter
roses in Lyanna's lap.
Blue as frost.
How many tens of
thousands had to die
because Rhaegar chose your aunt?
Yes, he chose her.
And then he kidnapped
her and raped her.
Come.
Let's speak somewhere
the dead can't hear us.
You're dressed for riding.
I am.
Where are you going?
King's Landing.
King's Landing?
Cersei sent for me.
We mustn't let her
sniff out any trouble.
You can't leave me here.
I know how hard it is to live
with people you despise.
Believe me.
But it won't be for long.
How do you know?
Stannis Baratheon
garrisons at Castle Black.
He'll march south
to King's Landing
before the winter snows
block his way.
But first he has
to take Winterfell.
- You don't know that.
- I do.
Once he liberates these
lands from the Boltons,
he'll rally your father's
bannermen to his cause.
With the North behind him,
Stannis can finally take
the Iron Throne.
You think he'll
defeat the Boltons?
He has a larger army.
He's the finest military
commander in Westeros.
A betting man would put
his money on Stannis.
As it happens,
I am a betting man.
And if you're right?
Stannis takes Winterfell,
he rescues you from the most
despised family in the North.
Grateful for your late father's
courageous support of his claim,
he names you
Wardeness of the North.
But I...
I wouldn't...
Wardeness of the North?
You are the last
surviving Stark.
He needs you.
And what if you're wrong?
What if Stannis never
attacks Winterfell?
Or he does and the
Boltons defeat him?
Then you will take
this Bolton boy, Ramsay,
and make him yours.
I don't know how to do that.
Of course you do.
He's already fallen for you.
His father frightens me.
He should. He's a dangerous man.
But even the most dangerous
men can be outmaneuvered.
And you've learned to
maneuver from the very best.
I'll return before too long.
You'll be strong without me.
The North will be yours.
Do you believe me?
I expect I'll be a married
woman by the time you return.
( Pats )
( groans )
( panting )
( blade scraping )
Breakfast.
That would have been
a shit way to die.
As far as I've seen, they're
all shit ways to die.
Aye, but your lot have to give
the singers a good ending.
I don't care what's sung
about me when I'm dead.
No?
Two knights off
to rescue a princess.
Sounds like a good song to me.
Sounds like all the rest.
What about you?
What shit way would you choose?
In my own keep
drinking my own wine
watching my sons
grovel for my fortune.
How disappointing.
I thought you'd have something
more exciting planned.
I've had an exciting life.
I want my death to be boring.
How do you want to go?
In the arms of the woman I love.
She want the same thing?
Let's go.
The captain of that ship...
What was he, Braavosi?
Pentoshi.
And he's headed to Oldtown?
As I said. Why?
What's to stop him from
docking down the coast
and telling the locals that
Jaime Lannister is in Dorne?
A bag of gold.
I'm not sure you understand
how much people hate your family
in this part of the world.
It was a heavy bag.
And I bet he swore all
kinds of oaths to get it.
But you won't be around
if he breaks 'em.
- ( Horse neighs )
- ( hoofbeats )
Bronn: How many you count?
Four.
How many do you think
you can take?
One if he's slow.
Halt!
Over the hill.
Fucked in the ass.
Hyah!
Morning, lads.
Glad we found you.
Who are you?
Cooper.
This is Darnell.
You're from King's Landing.
Accent gave me away?
Flea Bottom,
whelped and whipped.
Why are you here?
Our ship capsized in the night.
We managed to swim ashore.
It was a near thing, really.
Thought the sharks would get us.
There are no sharks in Dorne.
Could have sworn
those were shark fins.
Dolphins, maybe.
Throw your swords in the sand.
Boys, there's no need for this.
Just point us
in the right direction,
we'll find our way home.
Swords in the sand now.
( Grunts )
Hyah! Hyah!
( Horse neighs )
That one should be slow enough.
( Shouts )
( shouts )
( grunts )
Bronn: Nice move.
Luck.
You had a wonderful teacher.
Always wanted
a Dornish stallion.
Beasts can run a day and
night without tiring.
We'll ride to the Water Gardens
with a nice breeze in our faces.
First we need
to bury these bodies.
Birds have to eat, too.
Corpses raise questions.
Questions raise armies.
We're not here to start a war.
Do you know how long it'll take
us to dig all those holes?
I can't dig very well
with one hand.
Not at all, really.
Mama.
Nym, Obara.
Will it be war?
Prince Doran will weep for
your father, but nothing else.
We must avenge Oberyn ourselves.
Without Doran, we have no army
to march against the Lannisters.
We don't need an army
to start a war.
Queen Cersei loves her children.
And we have one of them.
You may have a problem.
( Groaning )
A ship's captain who
found me in Planky Town
claiming he had
information to sell.
He told me he smuggled
Jaime Lannister into Dorne.
He's come for Myrcella.
If he gets to her before we do,
we lose our only chance
for revenge.
You must choose.
Doran's way and peace,
or my way and war.
I'm with you always.
Nym?
Obara?
When I was a child, Oberyn
came to take me to court.
I had never seen this man,
and yet he called
himself my father.
My mother wept,
said I was too young and a girl.
Oberyn tossed his spear
at my feet and said,
"Girl or boy,
we fight our battles,
but the gods let us
choose our weapons."
My father pointed to the spear
and then to my mother's tears.
( Grunts )
I made my choice long ago.
( Tyrion muffled )
Will you untie me?
( Muffled )
Will you please untie me?
( muffled groan )
Will you please?
( Muffled singing )
Thank you.
Who are you?
Your captor.
Do you have wine?
No.
Can't sleep without wine.
Then stay awake.
You're going the wrong way.
My sister is in Westeros.
Westeros is west.
We're heading east.
I'm not taking you
to your sister.
You said you were
taking me to the queen.
I am. Queen Daenerys Targaryen.
She's the queen I serve.
( laughing )
What a waste
of a good kidnapping.
It so happens I was
heading there myself.
What business would you
have with the queen?
Gold and glory. Oh, and hate.
If you'd ever met my sister,
you'd understand.
So, now that it's clear
we are on the same side...
A highborn knight from
the North of Westeros
down on his luck in Essos.
Dragon epaulets,
bear sigil breastplate.
You're Jorah Mormont.
I have to ask.
How exactly were you
serving your queen
in a whorehouse
half a world away?
Is it possible
that you were running?
Why would you be running?
And why would she
have sent you away?
Oh, wait.
You were spying
on her, weren't you?
It's all coming back to me.
I was drunk through most of
the small council meetings,
but it's all coming back.
You passed notes
to Varys's little birds.
She found out, didn't she?
Found out and exiled you.
Now you hope to win back
her favor with a gift.
Risky scheme.
One might even say desperate.
You think Daenerys will
execute me and pardon you?
I'd say the reverse
is just as likely.
( Bird screeches )
Everyone looks happy
enough from up here.
- ( laughs )
- What?
I was thinking about
all the times your brother
made me go with him
down from the Red Keep
into the streets
of King's Landing.
- Why?
- He liked to walk among the people.
He liked to sing to them.
He sang to them?
- Yes.
- ( laughs )
Rhaegar would pick
a spot on the Hook
or the Street of Seeds
and then he'd sing.
Just like all
the other minstrels.
And what did you do?
I made sure no one killed him.
And I collected the money.
What? He liked to see
how much he could make.
- He was good?
- He was very good.
Viserys never told you?
He told me Rhaegar
was good at killing people.
Rhaegar never liked killing.
He loved singing.
And what did you do
with the money?
Well, one time, he gave it to the
next minstrel down the street.
One time, he gave it to an
orphanage in Flea Bottom.
One time, we got horribly drunk.
( laughs )
Your Grace.
Hizdahr is here, waiting
in the audience chamber.
How many others are there?
50? 100?
Will you be joining us,
Ser Barristan?
I think I can protect you
from Hizdahr zo Loraq.
I think I can protect me
Go, Ser Barristan.
Sing a song for me.
Your Grace.
All men must die, but not
all can die in glory.
- Glory?
- Why else do men fight?
Why did your ancestors
cross the Narrow Sea
and conquer the Seven Kingdoms?
So their names would live on.
Those who find victory
in the fighting pits
will never become kings,
but their names will live on.
It's the best chance
they'll ever have.
Is that what
you used to tell men
before you set them to
butchering each other for sport?
Your Grace, today is the traditional
start of the fighting season.
I do not recognize
this tradition.
Traditions are the only thing
that will hold this city,
your city, together.
Without them, former
slaves and former masters
have nothing in common.
Nothing but centuries
of mistrust and resentment.
I can't promise this is the
answer to all our problems,
but it's a start.
( speaking Valyrian )