( wind howling )
- Man: Look out!
- Man ♪2: Fire! Fire!
Davos: A band of 20
men, maybe less.
They were in and out
before anyone spotted them.
Burnt our food stores
to the ground,
all our siege weapons destroyed.
- Dozens of tents were...
- Horses?
We're still getting a count,
but hundreds are dead.
20 men rode into our camp without a
single guard sounding the alarm?
The northerners know more about
their land than we ever will.
Put last night's guards
in chains.
Either they fell asleep or
they conspired with the enemy.
- Find out the truth and then hang them.
- Your Grace.
Unless there's a thaw, we can't
press forward to Winterfell
and we don't have enough food
to get us back to Castle Black.
We're not returning
to Castle Black.
Forgive me, Your Grace, I never claimed
to be an expert in military matters,
but if we can't march forward
and we won't march back...
Have the dead horses
butchered for meat.
Man: Halt!
- Man ♪2: Halt!
- ( men coughing )
Man: Halt!
- Man ♪3: There it is!
- ( horse whinnies )
Open the gates.
Jon: It was a failure.
It wasn't.
( Baby crying )
I went to save them. I failed.
You didn't fail him.
Or him.
Or her.
You didn't fail him.
Every one of them is alive
because of you and no one else.
You didn't fail him.
I don't think that
fact's lost on them.
You have a good heart, Jon Snow.
It'll get us all killed.
Alliser: Out of my way.
( Horse neighs )
( men shouting )
( horse neighs )
( sighs )
You sent for me, Your Grace?
Find some healthy horses and
a few knights to guard you.
You sent for me, Your Grace?
I'm sending you back
to Castle Black.
You sent for me, Your Grace?
Tell the Lord Commander
his king commands him
You sent for me, Your Grace?
To send food, supplies,
fresh horses.
You sent for me, Your Grace?
In return,
when I take the throne,
You sent for me, Your Grace?
I'll make sure the Night's Watch
has all the men it requires.
You sent for me, Your Grace?
He can guard all 19 castles
on the Wall if he so wishes.
You sent for me, Your Grace?
Your Grace,
you named me your Hand.
Yes.
Your Grace,
you named me your Hand.
The King's Hand should
never abandon the king,
Your Grace,
you named me your Hand.
Especially in time of war.
Your Grace,
you named me your Hand.
You're not abandoning me.
You're obeying a command.
Your Grace,
you named me your Hand.
A boy with a scroll
could deliver this message.
Your Grace,
you named me your Hand.
And if Jon Snow refuses
the boy with the scroll,
Your Grace,
you named me your Hand.
What does the boy say?
Your Grace,
you named me your Hand.
I didn't name you Hand for your
expertise in military matters.
Your Grace,
you named me your Hand.
Ride for Castle Black.
Don't come back empty-handed.
Your Grace,
you named me your Hand.
Your Grace, perhaps Queen Selyse
and Princess Shireen
could accompany me.
Your Grace, perhaps Queen Selyse
My family stays with me.
At least let me take Shireen.
Your Grace, perhaps Queen Selyse
A siege is no place
for a little girl.
Your Grace, perhaps Queen Selyse
My family stays with me.
( men coughing )
What's this one now?
"The Dance of Dragons:
A True Telling"
What's this one now?
By Grand Maester Munkun.
Now that sounds
like a proper story.
What's this one now?
Ser Byron Swann wanted
to kill the dragon Vhagar.
What's this one now?
He polished his shield for a week
so that it was like a mirror.
What's this one now?
And he crouched behind it
and crept forward,
What's this one now?
Hoping the dragon would
only see its own reflection.
What's this one now?
But the dragon saw a dumb man
holding a mirrored shield.
What's this one now?
And burnt him to a crisp.
( laughs )
What's this one now?
Thus ending
the dragon-slaying career
What's this one now?
Of Ser Byron Swann. ( laughs )
I made you something, Princess.
Do you like it?
He's beautiful.
- Thank you.
- You're very welcome.
Do you like it?
Will you make me a doe, too?
So that he can have company?
Do you like it?
Of course I will.
But why am I getting a present?
Because you deserve it.
My son was always on me,
trying to teach me to read.
Because you deserve it.
Gods, I was stubborn about it.
Made it this far
without reading.
Seemed to me I could
make it to the grave.
Made it this far
without reading.
Wish I'd listened to him.
This is my own poor way
of saying thank you.
For teaching me
to be a grown-up.
I'll be gone for a
few days, Princess.
I want to hear all about "The
Dance of Dragons" when I'm back.
I'll be gone for a
few days, Princess.
You'll read it yourself.
I'll be gone for a
few days, Princess.
( Birds chirping )
Prince Doran.
Forgive us.
We started without you.
Prince Doran.
Please, sit.
Princess Myrcella.
Uncle.
Please, sit.
What a lovely dress.
- You don't like it?
- You must be cold.
Please, sit.
Not at all. The Dornish
climate agrees with me.
Please, sit.
Prince Trystane.
How's your jaw?
A fleabite.
What are you doing in Dorne?
Looking after the safety of my
niece, the Princess Myrcella.
A fleabite.
And rather than send a raven
or speak to me directly,
A fleabite.
You decided to enter
my country in secret
A fleabite.
And abduct our guest by force?
We received
a threatening message.
A fleabite.
The princess's necklace
in the jaws of a viper.
A fleabite.
That necklace
was stolen from my room.
Oh, excellent.
A last meal before
the beheading?
Oh, excellent.
Oh, I can't behead you.
Many in Dorne want war.
Oh, excellent.
But I've seen war.
I've seen the bodies
piled on the battlefields.
Oh, excellent.
I've seen the orphans
starving in the cities.
Oh, excellent.
I don't want to lead
my people into that hell.
Oh, excellent.
No, you want to break bread
with the Lannisters.
Oh, excellent.
And that is precisely
what we are doing.
Oh, excellent.
Let us drink to Tommen,
the First of His Name,
King of the Andals
and the First Men,
Let us drink to Tommen,
the First of His Name,
Lord of the Seven Kingdoms.
Let us drink to Tommen,
the First of His Name,
( slams )
King Tommen insists
on his sister's return
to the capital?
King Tommen insists
I'm afraid he does.
I cannot disobey
my king's command.
She will return with you
to King's Landing.
I cannot disobey
my king's command.
And my son Prince Trystane
will accompany you both.
I cannot disobey
my king's command.
If the alliance between the Iron
Throne and Dorne is to continue,
I cannot disobey
my king's command.
Their engagement must stand.
I cannot disobey
my king's command.
I accept.
I cannot disobey
my king's command.
One more thing.
My brother was named
I cannot disobey
my king's command.
To the small council
before his death.
I cannot disobey
my king's command.
Your father understood
the importance
I cannot disobey
my king's command.
Of keeping Dorne in the fold.
I cannot disobey
my king's command.
With Oberyn gone, Trystane will take
his place on the small council.
I cannot disobey
my king's command.
You have my word.
I cannot disobey
my king's command.
The word of a kingslayer.
I cannot disobey
my king's command.
No wonder you can't stand.
You have no spine.
You are mother
to four of my nieces,
No wonder you can't stand.
You have no spine.
Girls I love very much.
No wonder you can't stand.
You have no spine.
For their sake, I hope you
live a long and happy life.
No wonder you can't stand.
You have no spine.
Speak to me that way
again, and you won't.
No wonder you can't stand.
You have no spine.
May I inquire as to the
fate of my man Bronn?
Tell me, Ser Jaime,
in King's Landing,
May I inquire as to the
fate of my man Bronn?
How do they punish a commoner
who strikes a prince?
May I inquire as to the
fate of my man Bronn?
He said it was just a fleabite.
May I inquire as to the
fate of my man Bronn?
The fault is mine.
Bronn is merely a soldier
following my orders.
The fault is mine.
If anyone should
be punished, it's me.
The fault is mine.
Prince Trystane must learn
judgment if he is to rule one day.
The fault is mine.
I'll let him decide.
I have learned the value
of mercy from my father.
-  I'll set your man free.
- You're a good man.
I have learned the value
of mercy from my father.
On one condition.
I have learned the value
of mercy from my father.
( Hands slapping )
I have learned the value
of mercy from my father.
Why do we play?
I'm better than you.
I'll always be better than you.
Why do we play?
I'm better than you.
Have I ever missed once?
Why do we play?
I'm better than you.
I don't think I have.
I can't recall.
Why do we play?
I'm better than you.
You must love humiliation.
Or pain.
Why do we play?
I'm better than you.
Which do you love most,
humiliation or pain?
Why do we play?
I'm better than you.
That one hurt, didn't it?
- ( Smacks )
- You going to cry?
That one hurt, didn't it?
Give up, little sister.
- You're going to miss.
- Oh, I never miss.
That one hurt, didn't it?
You will.
You're thinking too much.
That one hurt, didn't it?
Now you're nervous.
What if she's right?
That one hurt, didn't it?
- Luck.
- Now it's my turn.
You're too slow.
- Luck.
- Now it's my turn.
You've always been too slow.
- Luck.
- Now it's my turn.
( Cell door unlocks )
Am I gonna be happy
at the end of this walk?
You'll find out very soon.
Am I gonna be happy
at the end of this walk?
Say it one more time, handsome.
Who am I?
The most beautiful
woman in the world.
And that's the truth.
The most beautiful
woman in the world.
- Slut.
-  ( Tyene laughs )
The most beautiful
woman in the world.
Prince Doran,
The most beautiful
woman in the world.
Ser Bronn of the Blackwater.
The most beautiful
woman in the world.
I didn't realize there were
knights of the Blackwater.
The most beautiful
woman in the world.
Only the one.
The most beautiful
woman in the world.
I believe you've already
met Prince Trystane.
The most beautiful
woman in the world.
Prince.
The most beautiful
woman in the world.
Sorry about the other day.
The most beautiful
woman in the world.
Jaime: Prince Trystane
here is a man of mercy.
The most beautiful
woman in the world.
He's agreed to grant
you your freedom.
The most beautiful
woman in the world.
I'm glad to hear it.
Pie looks good.
There was one condition.
( Grunts )
( Bronn groans )
Perhaps some soup instead.
- ( merchants shouting ) - Arya:
Oysters, clams, and cockles.
Oysters, clams, and cock...
How much for your little clam?
Oysters, clams, and cockles.
( laughs )
Come on.
Some oysters, girl!
I'm talking to you.
Is, uh...
Some oysters, girl!
- Girl!
- Man: Tie her up!
Thin Man: Are you deaf? Girl!
- Girl!
- Man: Tie her up!
Girl!
My lord.
Sailor: My lord.
Tycho: Lord Tyrell.
On behalf of the Iron Bank,
Sailor: My lord.
May I be the first
to welcome you
Sailor: My lord.
To the Free City of Braavos.
I hope your journey
was trouble-free.
Sailor: My lord.
A bit of chop the last few days.
Nothing too awful.
Sailor: My lord.
Good to see the old chap
still guarding the harbor.
Sailor: My lord.
And how goes the
harvest in the Reach?
Sailor: My lord.
Ah, the vintners say
this might be
Sailor: My lord.
The best year for red
grapes in half a century.
Sailor: My lord.
If we come to a
satisfactory arrangement,
Sailor: My lord.
I'll be sure to send a cask of
the Arbor's finest your way.
Sailor: My lord.
I'm afraid I don't partake.
Oh.
Sailor: My lord.
Some consider usury
distasteful, dishonorable.
Pure nonsense, of course.
Some consider usury
distasteful, dishonorable.
I'm glad we see eye to
eye on this matter.
Some consider usury
distasteful, dishonorable.
Mace: Did you know that at
one point Maegor the third
Some consider usury
distasteful, dishonorable.
Tried to outlaw it
in the Seven Kingdoms?
Some consider usury
distasteful, dishonorable.
Wanted to arrest anyone
caught charging interest
Some consider usury
distasteful, dishonorable.
And cut off both their hands.
Some consider usury
distasteful, dishonorable.
Most unfortunate
for the glovers.
Some consider usury
distasteful, dishonorable.
Mace: If a man charges
no interest on a loan,
Some consider usury
distasteful, dishonorable.
Then he has nothing to gain
and everything to lose,
Some consider usury
distasteful, dishonorable.
So why chance it?
Some consider usury
distasteful, dishonorable.
Whereas the promise of reward
Some consider usury
distasteful, dishonorable.
Makes a man willing to gamble.
Some consider usury
distasteful, dishonorable.
We are not gamblers here at
the Iron Bank, Lord Tyrell.
Some consider usury
distasteful, dishonorable.
You are the world's
best gamblers.
Some consider usury
distasteful, dishonorable.
And all those bets
you won built this.
Some consider usury
distasteful, dishonorable.
( Coins clink )
( door opens )
( coins clink )
Mace: We should celebrate.
( Coins clink )
Tycho: I'm afraid I still have
a good deal of work to do.
( Coins clink )
Mace: Oh, nonsense. Work's over.
Do you sing?
( coins clink )
- I don't have that gift.
- Oh, it's not a gift.
( Coins clink )
It's a skill.
Anyone can learn it.
( Coins clink )
♪ So give me a kiss
by the Long Canal ♪
( Coins clink )
♪ And give me two kisses
in Salty Town ♪
( Coins clink )
♪ For we're going
to die tomorrow ♪
( Coins clink )
♪ The bareheaded beggar,
the king with his crown... ♪
( Coins clink )
Trant: Thought that old shit
would never stop singing.
( coins clink )
Wasn't bad, though.
( Coins clink )
The Tyrells can all rot in hell.
Treasonous cunts.
( Coins clink )
They were going to make
that boy-fucker Renly king.
( Coins clink )
This is the place, lads.
The sleekest little minks
in Braavos.
This is the place, lads.
- You buying?
- Oh, I'm buying.
This is the place, lads.
But I never was good at sharing.
- ( Chatter, laughter )
-  ( music playing )
Sell your fish somewhere else.
Oh, let her in, Brusco.
I'm hungry.
Sell your fish somewhere else.
Come here, sweetness.
They say oysters
get the juices flowing.
We'll take half a dozen.
They say oysters
get the juices flowing.
Three coppers.
Here's a silver because
the lady likes you.
Three coppers.
Too old.
Brea.
Madame: I have just the one.
Anara.
Our most expensive girl.
But well worth it, I assure you.
Too old.
Do you have what I want or not?
Of course. Of course.
- ( Gasps )
- These fresh?
Come on, the lads are hungry.
Nothing better for your
cockstand than fresh oysters.
- Guard: Here. Thank you.
- Guard ♪2: I'll have one.
Nothing better for your
cockstand than fresh oysters.
Any vinegar?
Who let this girl in?
Shoo! Shoo!
( Guards chuckle )
Who let this girl in?
Shoo! Shoo!
Good.
I'll tell you when we're done.
You'll have a fresh one
for me tomorrow?
Of course.
You'll have a fresh one
for me tomorrow?
Madame: I'll have
you whipped, girl.
Go, go on. Out, out, go.
Madame: I'll have
you whipped, girl.
( whispering )
Valar morghulis.
And?
The thin man
wasn't hungry today.
And?
Perhaps that is why
a man is thin.
And?
Tomorrow.
- Tomorrow.
-  ( thuds )
And?
A girl has work to do.
Your rebellion is over.
You can swear your
allegiance to me now...
Your rebellion is over.
Or you can die.
( Crying )
I believe in second chances.
I don't believe
in third chances.
You write like a seven-year-old.
Your maester kindly agreed
to copy it over for me.
You write like a seven-year-old.
He didn't try to make you pay?
Mm-mmm.
You write like a seven-year-old.
Maybe he's changed.
The queen will be thrilled to know
you're bringing her daughter home.
You write like a seven-year-old.
She will.
You love her very much,
don't you?
You write like a seven-year-old.
Of course, she's my niece.
I wasn't talking about her.
You write like a seven-year-old.
You think I disapprove?
Why?
Because people disapprove of that
sort of thing where you are from?
You think I disapprove?
They disapproved of Oberyn
and me where you are from.
You think I disapprove?
Here no one blinked an eye.
100 years ago,
no one would have
blinked an eye at you
100 years ago,
if you'd been named Targaryen.
It's always changing, who we're
supposed to love and who we're not.
The only thing
that stays the same
is that we want who we want.
The only thing
that stays the same
I know your daughter had no
part in the terrible thing
that happened to the man I love.
I know your daughter had no
part in the terrible thing
Perhaps even you
are innocent of that.
( Horse whinnying )
( tent flap rustles )
Father.
( Tent flap rustles )
Aren't you cold?
No. What are you reading?
- "The Dance of Dragons."
- What's it about?
No. What are you reading?
It's the story of the fight
between Rhaenyra Targaryen
No. What are you reading?
And her half-brother Aegon for
control over the Seven Kingdoms.
No. What are you reading?
Both of them thought they
belonged on the Iron Throne.
No. What are you reading?
When people started declaring
for one of them or the other,
No. What are you reading?
Their fight divided
the kingdoms in two.
No. What are you reading?
Brothers fought brothers,
dragons fought dragons.
No. What are you reading?
By the time it was over,
thousands were dead.
And it was a disaster
for the Targaryens as well.
By the time it was over,
thousands were dead.
They never truly recovered.
By the time it was over,
thousands were dead.
"The Dance of Dragons."
By the time it was over,
thousands were dead.
Why is that a dance?
It's just what they call it.
Hmm, doesn't make much sense.
Why is that a dance?
I think it's poetic.
If you had to choose
between Rhaenyra and Aegon...
who would you have chosen?
I wouldn't have chosen either.
Who would you have chosen?
It's all the choosing sides that
made everything so horrible.
Who would you have chosen?
Sometimes a person
has to choose.
Who would you have chosen?
Sometimes the world
forces his hand.
If a man knows what he is...
and remains true to himself...
the choice is no choice at all.
He must fulfill his destiny...
And become
who he is meant to be.
However much he may hate it.
It's all right, Father.
You don't even know
what I'm talking about.
It's all right, Father.
It doesn't matter.
I want to help you.
It's all right, Father.
Is there any way I can help?
Yes, there is.
Good. I want to.
I'm the Princess Shireen
of House Baratheon.
And I'm your daughter.
I'm the Princess Shireen
of House Baratheon.
( Sighs )
Forgive me.
Where's my father?
I want to see my father.
It will all be over
soon, Princess.
Where's my father?
I want to see my father.
( Crying ) No.
Where's my father?
No, you can't do this.
Father, where are you?
Where's my father?
Please, let me see my father.
Father, where are you?
Don't let her do this.
Where's my father?
Please let go!
Let me see my father!
Where are you? Please!
Please let go!
- Selyse: It's what the Lord wants.
- Shireen: No.
Please let go!
-  Please! Let go! No!
- It's a good thing.
Please let go!
- A great thing.
- Shireen: Stop. Stop!
Please let go!
- Shireen: Please!
- Melisandre: Hear us now, my Lord.
Please let go!
- Shireen: You can't do this!
- Melisandre:  For you, we offer up this girl
Please let go!
- Please! - ...that you may
cleanse her with your fire
Please let go!
And that its light
may lead our way.
Please let go!
Shireen: Please! No, please
let me see my father.
Please let go!
If we don't act,
we'll all starve here.
Please let go!
- All of us.
- ( Shireen crying )
Please let go!
But if we make this sacrifice...
Melisandre: Accept this token
of our faith, my Lord,
Please let go!
And lead us from the darkness.
- Lord of Light, show us the way.
- Mother!
Please let go!
Mother, please!
Mother, please! Mother!
-  Mother!
- We can't.
Mother, please! Mother!
- There's no other way. She has king's blood.
-  Please don't do this!
Mother, please! Mother!
Melisandre: Lord of
Light, protect us.
Mother, please! Mother!
- Please! Father, please!
-  For the night is dark and full of terrors.
Mother, please! Mother!
Father!
Father, don't do this! Please!
Mother, please! Mother!
Mother, no! Please!
Please, help!
Mother, please! Mother!
Don't do this!
Please, Father! Mother, help!
Mother, please! Mother!
- No.
-  No, please! Don't do this!
Mother, please! Mother!
Don't do this, please, Mother!
Please, Mother! Mother, help!
Mother, please! Mother!
Mother, help! Help!
Please don't do this, Mother!
Mother, please! Mother!
Please!
Please, Mother! Please!
Mother, please! Mother!
Please! No!
- ( Fire crackling )
- ( Shireen screaming )
Mother, please! Mother!
( Screaming stops )
No!
( Applause, cheering )
( applause, cheering continue )
( drums beating )
( drumming stops )
Where have you been?
Just making sure
everything is in order.
Where have you been?
- ( Horse neighs )
- ( gate opens )
Where have you been?
( Cheering )
( Cheering stops )
( speaking Valyrian )
( cheering stops )
( cheering )
They're waiting for you.
Clap your hands.
( Cheering )
( both grunting )
- ( groans )
-  ( Daario chuckles )
That one, the smaller man.
- ( Groans )
-  ( Daario chuckles )
No question, that's where
you should put your money.
- ( Groans )
-  ( Daario chuckles )
The smaller man it is.
- ( Groans )
-  ( Daario chuckles )
I'm not putting
my money anywhere.
- ( Groans )
-  ( Daario chuckles )
Kings and queens
never bet on the games.
- ( Groans )
-  ( Daario chuckles )
Perhaps you should go
find someone who does.
- ( Groans )
-  ( Daario chuckles )
People used to bet against me
when I fought in the pits.
- ( Groans )
-  ( Daario chuckles )
He would have bet against me.
Common novice mistake.
- ( Groans )
-  ( Daario chuckles )
I've spent much
of my life in this arena.
- ( Groans )
-  ( Daario chuckles )
And in my experience,
large men do triumph
- ( groans )
-  ( Daario chuckles )
over smaller men
far more often than not.
- ( Groans )
-  ( Daario chuckles )
Has your experience ever
involved any actual fighting?
- ( Groans )
-  ( Daario chuckles )
You yourself?
- ( Groans )
-  ( Daario chuckles )
Have you ever tried to kill another
man who was trying to kill you?
- ( Groans )
-  ( Daario chuckles )
Whenever I got into the pit
against a beast like that one,
the crowd saw me, all
skin and bone back then,
Whenever I got into the pit
against a beast like that one,
then they saw a pile of angry
muscles ready to murder me.
Whenever I got into the pit
against a beast like that one,
They couldn't get their
money out fast enough.
Whenever I got into the pit
against a beast like that one,
But the pile of angry muscles
never had any muscles here
Whenever I got into the pit
against a beast like that one,
or... here.
Whenever I got into the pit
against a beast like that one,
And the big men
were always too slow
Whenever I got into the pit
against a beast like that one,
to stop my dagger from going
where their muscles weren't.
Whenever I got into the pit
against a beast like that one,
Yes, whenever I saw a beast like
that one standing across from me
Whenever I got into the pit
against a beast like that one,
making his beast faces,
I knew I could rest easy.
Whenever I got into the pit
against a beast like that one,
- ( shouting )
-  ( crowd cheering )
Whenever I got into the pit
against a beast like that one,
You don't approve?
There's always been more than enough
death in the world for my taste.
You don't approve?
I can do without it
in my leisure time.
You don't approve?
Fair enough. Yet it's
an unpleasant question,
You don't approve?
But what great thing has ever been
accomplished without killing or cruelty?
You don't approve?
It's easy to confuse what is
with what ought to be,
You don't approve?
Especially when what is
has worked out in your favor.
You don't approve?
I'm not talking about myself.
I'm talking about the necessary
conditions for greatness.
You don't approve?
That is greatness?
That is a vital part of the
great city of Meereen,
You don't approve?
Which existed
long before you or I
You don't approve?
And will remain standing long after
we have returned to the dirt.
You don't approve?
My father would have liked you.
-  ( Gate opens )
- ( crowd cheering )
You don't approve?
( Speaking Valyrian )
One day your great city will
return to the dirt as well.
( Speaking Valyrian )
- At your command?
- If need be.
( Speaking Valyrian )
( crowd cheering )
- ( warrior speaking Valyrian ) - And how
many people will die to make this happen?
If it comes to that, they will
have died for a good reason.
- ( Warrior speaking Valyrian ) - And how
many people will die to make this happen?
Those men think they're
dying for a good reason.
- ( Warrior speaking Valyrian ) - And how
many people will die to make this happen?
Someone else's reason.
- ( Warrior speaking Valyrian ) - And how
many people will die to make this happen?
So your reasons are true
and theirs are false?
- ( Warrior speaking Valyrian ) - And how
many people will die to make this happen?
They don't know their
own minds, but you do?
- ( Warrior speaking Valyrian ) - And how
many people will die to make this happen?
Well said.
You're an eloquent man.
- ( Warrior speaking Valyrian ) - And how
many people will die to make this happen?
Doesn't mean you're wrong.
- ( Warrior speaking Valyrian ) - And how
many people will die to make this happen?
In my experience,
eloquent men are right
- ( warrior speaking Valyrian ) - And how
many people will die to make this happen?
Every bit as often as imbeciles.
- ( Warrior speaking Valyrian ) - And how
many people will die to make this happen?
( Jorah speaking Valyrian )
- Your Grace...
- Shut your mouth.
( Crowd cheering )
( both grunting )
- ( groans )
- ( cheering )
( man groans )
( groans )
- ( groans )
- ( cheering )
( applause )
( groans )
- You can end this.
- She cannot.
- You can.
- ( crowd chanting )
- You can end this.
- She cannot.
( Screams )
( crowd cheering )
( screams )
( shouting in Valyrian )
( booing )
( speaking Valyrian )
- ( grunts )
- ( crowd groans )
( groans )
- ( grunts )
- ( crowd groans )
( crowd booing )
- ( grunts )
- ( crowd groans )
( groans )
( people shouting )
( people screaming )
Protect your queen!
( People screaming )
( crowd screaming )
( people screaming )
Go!
Your Grace! Your Grace!
Come with me. I know a way out.
I know a way...
Your Grace! Your Grace!
( Groans )
( men shouting in Valyrian )
( Missandei screams )
Stay close.
This way.
The other side.
- Follow me.
-  ( people screaming )
The other side.
Protect your queen!
( shouts in Valyrian )
Drogon!
Valahd.