Valar morghulis.
Valar dohaeris.
I've been sweeping
this floor for days.
Good.
I didn't come here
to sweep floors.
No?
Why come, then?
You said I could be
your apprentice.
You said you'd teach me
how to be a Faceless Man.
A man teaches a girl.
Valar dohaeris.
All men must serve.
Faceless Men most of all.
I want to serve.
A girl wants to serve herself.
Here we serve
the Many-Faced God.
To serve well,
a girl must become no one.
Which one's the Many-Faced God?
I see the Stranger.
I see the Drowned God.
I see the weirwood face.
There is only one god.
A girl knows his name.
And all men know his gift.
Where are they taking him?
- ( Bells tolling )
- ( people shouting )
( people shouting ) Queen Margaery!
Queen Margaery!
Man: Queen Margaery!
- I am his and he is mine.
- I am hers and she is mine.
Both: From this day until
the end of my days.
( breathing heavily )
Did I hurt you?
No. You were lovely.
- It all happened so fast.
- Yes. ( chuckles )
I was scared maybe I hurt you.
- It sounded like...
- No, no, no.
You're very sweet.
The sweetest king
who ever lived.
This is all I want
to do all day,
every day,
for the rest of my life.
( laughs ) Wouldn't
that be glorious?
Shouldn't we rest
a little while?
Just to catch our breath?
There's no rush, is there?
Of course not.
Are you hungry?
Should I have them bring you
some cake or pomegranate juice?
No, I'm fine.
I just want you all to myself.
I want to know everything
there is to know
about King Tommen,
First of His Name.
King Tommen.
Still sounds strange to me.
Does Queen Margaery
sound strange to you?
So strange.
- Husband.
- Wife.
( laughs )
Sometimes it feels odd.
I'm the king,
I've married the most
beautiful woman in the world,
and it's all because
my brother died.
I understand.
But it's not your fault.
You know that, don't you?
You mustn't feel guilty.
I don't feel guilty.
That's what's odd.
Do you like to sail?
I love to sail.
I do, too.
I think we're going to be
very happy, you and I.
I do, too.
( Kisses )
Living in a tower so high
it touches the clouds.
Of course, my grandmother
couldn't wait to go home.
The capital's not
for everyone, I suppose.
Does your mother like it here?
I don't think so.
She told me never to trust
anyone in King's Landing.
It's so wonderful to have
her watching over you.
A lioness guarding her cub.
Well, but I'm a man now.
You are.
And the king.
But you'll always be
her baby boy.
- I suppose.
-  I adore her.
She's always been so
generous with me, so kind.
And the horrors
she's had to endure...
Losing her husband, her
eldest child, and her father.
It's no wonder she's
so protective of you.
She'll never let you
out of her sight.
Cersei: You look
very much in love.
The first days of marriage
are often so blissful.
She's certainly
very pretty, isn't she?
Like a doll.
She smiles quite a lot.
Do you think she's intelligent?
I can't quite tell.
Not that it matters.
Do you ever miss Casterly Rock?
There's nothing for me
in Casterly Rock.
That's where you grew up.
You always told me that you
liked the people there better.
You said that King's Landing smelled
of horse dung and sour milk.
( Chuckles )
Why are we speaking
of Casterly Rock?
The way that
you talked about it,
I always thought
that you missed it,
that you... that it
was your real home.
This is my real home now,
where my family lives.
I want you to be happy, Mother.
I know that.
I know you do.
My sweet boy.
But wouldn't you be
happier in Casterly Rock?
Margaery: I said, "Darling,
surely four times is enough."
-  ( women giggling ) - "Are you
trying to set a new record?"
He said, "Well, what is the record?
I'm sure we can break it."
( laughing )
Mother.
Welcome.
Don't you look lovely?
Marriage agrees with you.
Can we bring you
anything to eat or drink?
I wish we had some wine for you.
It's a bit early
in the day for us.
No, no, I can't stay.
I just wanted to let you know
if there's ever anything
I can do for you...
You are very sweet.
Tommen seems quite taken
with his new queen.
I absolutely adore him.
You raised a gallant young man.
I'm forever grateful.
Good.
Good. I'm glad to
hear you're happy.
Ecstatic. I really am.
Exhausted, to be honest.
But what could I expect?
He is half lion, half stag.
( Women laugh )
I'll leave you to it, then.
Oh, forgive me.
I haven't been
at court for long.
I get so confused.
What's the proper way
to address you now?
Queen Mother or Dowager Queen?
There's no need
for such formalities.
In any event, judging from
the king's enthusiasm,
the Queen Mother will be
a Queen Grandmother soon.
Won't that be a lovely day?
Can you imagine
the celebrations?
They'll ring the bells
all day and night.
Remember...
anything you need.
( Women giggle )
( laughing )
( laughter echoing )
( horse neighs )
( men shouting )
( animals squawking )
( flies buzzing )
( caws )
Roose: We can't hold the
North with terror alone.
Ramsay: You can't hold the North if
you let these lesser lords insult us.
Roose: I sent you there to
collect taxes, not bodies.
Ramsay:
Lord Cerwyn refused to pay.
Said the Warden of the North
would always be a Stark
and he'd be damned if he'd
kiss a traitor's boot.
Roose: He left you no choice.
I flayed him living along
with his wife and brother.
Made his son watch.
And?
The new Lord Cerwyn
paid his taxes.
I've something important
to tell you.
Stop eating and listen.
We don't have enough men
to hold the North
if the other houses
rise up against us.
Do you understand that?
Our pact with
the Lannisters protects...
I had a pact
with Tywin Lannister.
And Tywin Lannister is dead.
The remaining Lannisters are a thousand
miles away dealing with that fact.
They've never once in the
history of the Seven Kingdoms
sent their army this far north.
If you think they will
for us, you're a fool.
We've become a great house
by entering into alliances
with other houses
and parlaying those alliances
into greater power.
The best way to forge
a lasting alliance
isn't by peeling
a man's skin off.
The best way is marriage.
Now that you're a Bolton
by royal decree,
it's high time you married
a suitable bride.
And as it happens,
I've found the perfect girl to
solidify our hold on the North.
That's Moat Cailin.
Yes, a bit shabby, isn't it?
You've been here before?
On our way down
to King's Landing
with my father and Arya.
Where are you taking me?
Home.
The Boltons have Winterfell.
Your marriage proposal,
it wasn't for you.
No.
Roose Bolton
murdered my brother.
He betrayed my family.
He did.
He serves the Lannisters.
For now.
- I won't go.
- Winterfell is your home.
- Not anymore.
- Always.
You're a Stark. Dying your
hair doesn't change that.
You're Sansa Stark, eldest surviving
child of Ned and Catelyn Stark.
Your place is in the North.
I can't marry him.
You can't make me.
He is a traitor. A murderer!
You're not marrying
Roose Bolton.
No, you'll be marrying
his son and heir Ramsay.
One day he'll be Warden
of the North and you...
- No.
- Sansa.
No, you can't make me.
I will starve myself.
I will die before
I have to go there.
I won't force you
to do anything.
Don't you know by now
how much I care for you?
Say the word and we turn
the horses around,
but listen to me. Listen.
You've been running
all your life.
Terrible things happen to
your family and you weep.
You sit alone in a darkened
room mourning their fates.
You've been a bystander to tragedy from
the day they executed your father.
Stop being a bystander.
Do you hear me?
Stop running.
There's no justice in the world.
Not unless we make it.
You loved your family.
Avenge them.
( Horse neighs )
Man: Banners!
How do we get through there?
We don't.
We go around.
Takes us miles out of the way.
We'll lose sight of them.
Brienne: Doesn't matter.
I know where they're going.
Aren't you getting
a bit old to be a squire?
How did you end up
squiring for the Imp?
He hates that nickname.
Well, he's not here
to complain about it, is he?
I squired for a knight
named Ser Lorimer
during the War
of the Five Kings.
One night he had
a bit too much to drink
and he was famished,
so he borrowed a ham.
He borrowed it?
He wasn't a thief.
He was drunk and hungry
and he wasn't thinking.
I was drunk, too.
He gave me half the ham.
Next morning, one of the
guards saw him passed out
under a wagon with the
hambone still in his hand.
They hanged him that afternoon.
They tied the noose for me, too,
but Lord Tywin heard
my family name was Payne,
so he pardoned me
and sent me to King's Landing
to squire for his son.
As punishment for both of you.
It didn't seem that way.
Lord Tyrion was always
very good to me.
Yes, all your lords
have been very kind to you.
All except me.
Sorry you had to squire
for such a nasty person.
I'm not sorry. You're the
best fighter I've ever seen.
You beat the Hound.
I'm proud to be your squire.
I'm sorry I'm always
snapping at you.
If you didn't snap at me,
I wouldn't learn anything.
You want to be a knight, Pod?
Yes.
Starting tomorrow, we'll train
with a sword twice a day.
Before we ride in the morning and
after you make camp in the evening.
- And I'm going to show you how to ride properly.
- Thank you.
I can't knight you, but I
can teach you how to fight.
I suppose that's more important.
You weren't a knight,
but you were a Kingsguard
to Renly Baratheon, weren't you?
I was.
Lord Tyrion said
he was a good man.
He was.
How did you end up
serving Renly?
When I was a girl,
my father held a ball.
I'm his only living child, so he
wanted to make a good match for me.
He invited dozens
of young lords to Tarth.
I didn't want to go, but he
dragged me to the ballroom.
And it was wonderful.
None of the boys noticed
how mulish and tall I was.
They shoved each other
and threatened to duel
when they thought
it was their turn to dance.
They whispered in my ear
how they wanted to marry me and
take me back to their castles.
My father smiled at me
and I smiled at him.
I had never been so happy.
Till I saw a few
of the boys snickering.
And then they all
started to laugh.
They couldn't keep
the game going any longer.
They were toying with me.
"Brienne the Beauty"
they called me.
Great joke.
And I realized I was
the ugliest girl alive.
A great lumbering beast.
I tried to run away,
but Renly Baratheon
took me in his arms.
"Don't let them see your
tears," he told me.
"They're nasty little shits
and nasty little shits
aren't worth crying over."
He danced with me and none of the
other boys could say a word.
Renly was the king's
brother after all.
But wasn't he...?
Lord Tyrion said he was...
Yes, Pod, he liked men.
I'm not an idiot.
He didn't love me.
He didn't want me.
He danced with me
because he was kind
and didn't want to see me hurt.
He saved me from being a joke.
From that day
until his last day.
And I couldn't
save him in return.
Nothing's more hateful than failing
to protect the one you love.
One day I will avenge
King Renly.
But you said a shadow
murdered him.
How do you fight a shadow?
A shadow with the face
of Stannis Baratheon.
I know it was Stannis.
I know it in my heart.
Stannis is a man, not a shadow.
And a man can be killed.
- Lord Commander.
- Your Grace.
I'd like to speak alone.
Olly is my steward now
as I was
Lord Commander Mormont's.
I want him to attend my meetings
to learn from men with experience.
One day he might command.
Very well.
Have you considered my offer?
I have.
And I thank you for it.
You do me great honor.
All my life I wanted
to be Jon Stark.
Say the word and you will be.
But I have to refuse you.
I'm Lord Commander
of the Night's Watch.
My place is here.
I'm giving you the chance
to avenge your family,
to take back the castle
where you grew up.
To rule the North.
I wish I could fight beside you.
Believe me, I do.
But I swore a sacred vow
at the godswood.
I pledged my life
to the Night's Watch.
You're as stubborn
as your father.
And as honorable.
I can imagine no higher praise.
I didn't mean it as praise.
Honor got your father killed.
But if your mind's made up,
I won't try and dissuade you.
May I ask, Your Grace, how long
you plan to stay at Castle Black?
Are you bored of us already?
You saved us
from Mance Rayder's army.
We will never forget that.
But it's a question of survival.
The Night's Watch can't
continue to feed your men
and the wildling
prisoners indefinitely.
Winter is coming.
I know it.
We march on Winterfell
within the fortnight,
before the snows trap us here.
And the wildlings?
If they'd rather burn than
fight for me, so be it.
I leave their fate to you.
You could execute them.
That's the safest course.
Or you could see
if this Tormund fellow
is more willing to compromise
than Mance ever was.
I assume the brothers
of the Night's Watch
would rather see
the wildlings dead.
Most of the brothers, yes.
There's little love
for the free folk here.
You're the Lord Commander.
Your decision.
( Door opens )
You have many enemies
in Castle Black.
Have you considered sending
Alliser Thorne elsewhere?
Give him command
of Eastwatch-by-the-Sea.
I heard it was best
to keep your enemies close.
Whoever said that
didn't have many enemies.
Davos: He sees something in you.
Might not be apparent
from his tone,
but it's the truth.
He believes in you.
I'm sorry I disappointed him.
The king is a complicated man,
but he wants to do what's
right for the Seven Kingdoms.
As long as he's ruling them.
He's the one true king.
He has a blood right
to that throne.
I've sworn to stay clear of the
politics of the Seven Kingdoms.
Have you now?
How does the Night's
Watch vow go again?
I'll bet you've got it
memorized since you got here.
Night gathers
and now my watch begins.
No, not that bit.
The bit at the end.
I am the sword in the darkness,
the watcher on the walls,
the shield that guards
the realms of men.
-  I pledge my life...
- Right, that's enough.
The shield that guards
the realms of men.
That's what you swore to be.
Now, I'm not a learned man,
but the best way to help the
most people might not be sitting
in a frozen castle
at the edge of the world.
It just might mean
wading in the muck,
getting your boots dirty
and doing what needs to be done.
And what needs to be done?
As long as the Boltons
rule the North,
the North will suffer.
Just one man's opinion.
( Door closes )
( door opens )
What do you want?
Who are you?
- What?
- You, who walk in here
with a coin you never earned
whose value you do not respect.
Who are you?
No one.
Ow! Cunt!
A lie. A sad little lie.
Who are you?
I told you, I'm no...
Do that again, and...
Who are you?
You're about to find out.
What are you doing?
We were only playing.
The Game of Faces.
- A girl is not ready.
- Clearly not.
I am ready!
For what?
For whatever you want.
To be a Faceless Man.
To be no one.
Jaqen: Whose sword is that?
It belongs to Arya Stark.
Arya Stark's sword,
Arya Stark's clothes,
Arya Stark's stolen silver.
A man wonders
how is it that no one
came to be surrounded
by Arya Stark's things.
( Sighs )
( door closes )
What do we do with them
after we wash them?
Man: Open gate!
Man ♪2: Honor guard, stand to!
Man ♪3: Hold up. Easy.
Lady Sansa. Welcome.
Lord Bolton.
May I introduce my son
Ramsay Bolton?
It's an honor
to meet you, my lady.
I'll bring you
a bowl of hot water.
You must want to wash.
Thank you.
Welcome home, Lady Stark.
The North remembers.
( Men chatting )
Sam?
Maester Aemon?
He apologizes
for not being here.
He's not feeling well.
Take good care of him.
- Brothers.
- ( chatter stops )
As you all know too well, it's long
past time to dig a new latrine pit.
( Men laugh )
First Builder Yarwyck and I
have decided to appoint
a latrine captain
to oversee this crucial task.
( Men laugh )
Brian.
Seems like a good job
for a ginger.
( Men laugh )
- That's him!
- That's him.
Ser Alliser.
You have more experience than any
other ranger at Castle Black.
You proved your valor
many times over
while defending the Wall
from the wildling attack.
I name you First Ranger.
Men: Hear, hear!
( Pounding on tables )
Jon: Lord Janos.
I'm giving you command
of Greyguard.
Greyguard is a ruin.
Yes, the fort
is in a sorry state.
Restore it as best you can.
First Builder Yarwyck
can spare 10 of his...
Slynt: I was charged with the
defense of King's Landing
when you were soiling
your swaddling clothes.
Keep your ruin.
( Men shouting )
- All right, all right!
- ( shouting stops )
Enough of that.
You mistake me, my lord.
That was a command,
not an offer.
Pack your arms and armor,
say your farewells,
and ride for Greyguard.
I will not go meekly off
to freeze and die.
Give it to one of the fools
who cast a stone for you.
I will not have it.
Did you hear me, boy?
I will not have it!
Are you refusing
to obey my order?
You can stick your order
up your bastard ass.
( Men murmuring )
Take Lord Janos outside.
Olly, bring me my sword.
- Dolorous Edd: Get out.
- Slynt: You cannot do this!
Get your hands off me!
Scum, all of you!
If the boy thinks he can
frighten me, he's mistaken.
Yes, very mistaken.
Disgrace!
I have friends.
Important friends
in the capital.
- You'll see.
- Kneel!
If you have any
last words, my lord,
now's the time.
I was wrong.
You're the Lord Commander.
We all serve you. I'm sorry.
Not only for this, for
all I've done and said.
I was wrong.
My lord, please! Mercy! Mercy!
I'll go! I will! ( sobbing )
Please.
I'm afraid.
( Whimpering )
I've always been afraid.
( Sobbing )
( women giggling )
You have served us well, my son.
Thank you, Father.
Which of the Seven
will you worship today?
- The Maiden.
- Always the Maiden.
High Septon: And the Stranger.
- Two is extra, you realize?
- Yes, yes.
( Snaps fingers )
- ( gasps )
- What are you doing?
This establishment belongs
to Lord Petyr Baelish.
You can't... ( groans )
You have profaned our faith,
the faith of our fathers
and forefathers.
I am the High Septon of the...
- You are a sinner.
- ( groans )
And you shall be punished.
- ( Cracks )
- Ah!
( Woman laughs )
- Sinner.
- Sparrows: Sinner.
- Sparrows: Sinner. Sinner.
- Man: Repent!
- Sinner. Sinner.
- ( groans )
Sinner. Sinner.
- Man ♪2: Shame on you.
- Sparrows: Sinner. Sinner.
( Doors close )
Your Grace, Grand Maester,
Lord Tyrell, uh...
It doesn't matter.
As the High Septon
of the Faith of the Seven,
I give voice
to the will of the gods
and am their foremost
servant in this world.
An insult to me
is an insult to the gods.
An assault on my person
is an assault
on our very religion.
- You were assaulted?
- I was.
By those fanatics
who call themselves sparrows.
They humiliated me,
they beat me,
they left me naked and
bleeding on the cobblestones.
I am lucky to be alive.
I heard this assault began
in Littlefinger's brothel.
High Septon, this is a rather
shocking thing to hear.
High Septon: I tend to both the highest
born and the lowliest amongst us.
Even prostitutes may earn
the mercy of the Mother.
So you were ministering to the
needs of these devout prostitutes?
A man's private affairs
ought to stay private.
What do you want from us,
High Septon?
Justice. I ask that
you protect our faith
by arresting these criminals and
throwing them in the black cells.
I ask that you execute
their leader,
this so-called High Sparrow.
He's a threat to everything
we hold sacred.
- If he goes unpunished...
- And where do I find this man?
This High Sparrow?
I don't think this is
a good idea, Your Grace.
Nonsense, Ser Meryn. These
are deeply religious people.
Where can I find
the High Sparrow?
Man: Seven blessings.
- ( people coughing )
-  ( flies buzzing )
( baby crying )
- Man: Thank you.
- Man ♪2: Just a little more.
( baby continues crying )
Woman: Thank you.
Man ♪3: Thank you.
A young man said I'd find
the High Sparrow back here.
- Where is he?
- High Sparrow?
Sounds ridiculous, doesn't it?
Like Lord Duckling
or King Turtle.
Still, it's meant to.
We're often stuck with the
names our enemies give to us.
The notion that we're all equal
in the eyes of the Seven
doesn't sit well with some,
so they belittle me.
Woman ♪2:
Seven blessings to you.
Seven blessings to you, my dear.
It's only a name.
Quite an easy burden to bear.
Far easier than hers.
Cersei: Why no shoes?
Because I gave them away to
someone who needed them more.
We all do that.
It stops us from forgetting
what we really are.
Is that why you came
to King's Landing?
To remind everyone?
Everyone? Hard enough
job reminding myself.
Well, I tell them
no one's special
and they think I'm special
for telling them so.
Perhaps they're right.
It would be comforting to
believe that, wouldn't it?
Have the gods sent
you here to tempt me?
I hope not.
I had assumed you'd only
come here to arrest me
for that incident
with the High Septon.
An unacceptable way to treat
the chosen representative
of the gods in this world,
wouldn't you say?
Hypocrisy is a boil.
Lancing a boil
is never pleasant.
Although they could have been
more careful with the blade.
The High Septon came
to speak to me today.
He doesn't want me
to arrest you.
He wants me to execute you.
I wouldn't presume to know
your thoughts on the matter.
My thoughts on the matter
are in line with your own.
The High Septon's behavior was
corrosive, as was his attitude.
Having a man like that reside in the sept
eats away at the faith from the inside.
So now he resides in the
Red Keep dungeons instead.
The faith and the crown
are the two pillars
that hold up this world.
One collapses,
so does the other.
We must do everything necessary
to protect one another.
( Squeaking )
- ( flesh squelches )
- ( rat squeals )
- Your Grace.
-  Send a raven with this message
to Littlefinger at the Eyrie or
wherever he's slithering about.
At once, Your Grace.
How's your work coming along?
Very well.
You've made progress?
More than I expected.
- Still a way to go, but...
- Very good.
I'll leave you to it, then.
Make sure Littlefinger is clear on the
meaning of the word "immediately."
( bottles rattle )
Shh.
Easy, friend.
( People shouting )
Ramsay: She really is lovely.
I hope I can make her happy.
I hope so, too.
I've become quite fond of Lady
Sansa during our travels together.
She's suffered enough.
I'll never hurt her.
You have my word.
I've heard very little
about you,
which makes you quite a
rare thing as lords go.
I haven't been a lord very long.
I was a bastard.
And you're not anymore.
Allow me a moment alone
with Lord Baelish.
Yes, Father.
And thank you, Lord Baelish.
I'm forever in your debt.
He seems pleased.
Shouldn't he be?
I assure you,
she's still a virgin.
Tyrion never consummated
the marriage.
By the law of the land,
she is no man's wife.
Inspect her if you must.
I'll leave that
to the brothel keeper.
It's her name I need,
not her virtue.
Then I have delivered
everything I promised.
And you're prepared
for the consequences
when the Lannisters hear I've
wed Sansa Stark to Ramsay?
The Lannister name doesn't
mean what it once did.
Tywin is dead.
He kept his house in power
through sheer will.
Without him, Jaime has
one hand and no allies.
Tommen is a soft boy,
not a king to fear.
The queen will be enraged.
Queen Margaery adores Sansa.
Cersei is Queen Mother,
a title whose importance
wanes with each passing day.
And yet she still has friends,
men in important places whom
she can ask for favors.
A message for you
from Cersei Lannister.
A rider arrived from the
Eyrie shortly before dawn.
Apparently she thinks
you're still in the Vale.
A message for me, you say?
Strange that the seal is broken.
I'm sure you understand
my position, Lord Baelish.
If you receive word in the
night from the Queen Mother,
it does make me question
our new alliance.
The Lannisters made you one of
the great lords of Westeros,
yet here you are in the
North undermining them.
Why gamble with your position?
Every ambitious move
is a gamble.
You gambled when you drove a
dagger into Robb Stark's heart.
It appears that
your gamble paid off.
You're Warden of the North.
I had Tywin Lannister's backing.
Who supports me now? You?
The Eyrie is mine.
The last time
the lords of the Eyrie
formed an alliance
with the lords of the North,
they brought down the greatest
dynasty this world has ever known.
I'd like to borrow
one of your birds.
Cersei will expect a reply.
I'd like to read the reply.
I have to get out
of this wheelhouse.
Volantis is a large city.
I have to get out
of this wheelhouse.
The likelihood of you being spotted
here increases a hundredfold.
Mm, I have to get out
of this wheelhouse.
( Sighs ) I'm not sure how many new
ways I can find of saying this.
I will not be of any use
to Daenerys Targaryen
if I lose my mind.
I can't remember the last
face I saw that wasn't yours.
It's a perfectly good face.
I am losing my mind.
If anyone recognizes you,
you'll lose more than that.
Look, we are thousands
of miles from Westeros.
What am I?
One more drunk dwarf.
( Knocks )
- Driver: Whoa!
- ( horses neigh )
( seagull screeching )
( people shouting )
Woman: We have to go now.
Come on, hold it. Hold it.
Are you ready?
Slaves.
Yes, the Volantene masters
are very organized.
Flies for dung shovelers.
Hammers for builders.
Tears for whores.
Lest they forget.
( Woman speaking Valyrian )
( crowd repeating )
We should keep moving.
( Crowd repeating )
The only red priest
we had in King's Landing
was Thoros of Myr.
This one's much better-looking.
Stone Men.
Good luck stopping the spread
of greyscale with prayer.
You'd have better luck
dancing away the plague.
Shh.
We're going to meet the savior.
You should have told me.
Who doesn't want
to meet the savior?
Come on.
Let's find a brothel.
- ( People shouting )
- ( animals calling )
Man: Build your house in a day.
( speaking Valyrian )
It's even better luck
to suck a dwarf's cock.
See? We blend right in.
Just two more travelers
mad with lust.
Thank you.
( Sniffing )
What curious hair.
The Mother of Dragons!
( Men laugh )
It appears you're not
the only Targaryen supporter.
( Man laughs )
We were just heading
east to see you.
I've got a dragon for you.
How much to make him spit fire?
Someone who inspires
priests and whores
is worth taking seriously.
What makes you worth that much?
- I'm magic.
- I'll bet you bloody are.
( laughing )
Well, she's taken.
Where are you going?
I need to speak
to someone with hair.
- Hello.
- You've got no drink.
- You've got no money.
Do I look like
a man without money?
Never trust looks.
Until quite recently, I was one
of the richest men in the world.
( laughs )
Who needs wealth when you
can make a woman laugh?
I always pay my debts.
I'm well known for it.
You like her.
They all like her.
They all want to fuck a queen.
That's because
they've never met a queen.
You're just saying that.
You know how to spot a liar.
If I could pick any girl here,
I would pick you.
Why?
Because you have
a skeptical mind.
All right, then.
I'm warning you,
we're going to have
to wash you first.
Come on.
I'm... I'm sorry, I can't.
Of course you can. You're shy.
I'm not.
Have another drink.
Gladly, but this I can't do.
Believe me, no one is
more shocked than I am.
I hope it passes.
What will I do in my spare time?
Go for a piss. That's a start.
No need to worry. I was just...
Oh, I thought
you were someone else.
Show's almost over.
I'm sure there are girls inside
who'd be happy to oblige.
You've made
some kind of mistake.
Why don't you tell me what you
think you're doing and then...
I'm taking you to the queen.