I'm so sorry, my queen.
He was a good man.
"Barristan the Bold"
they called him.
He crossed a continent
to serve me.
He was a loyal friend.
And he died in an alley,
butchered by cowards
who hide behind masks.
We could pull back
to the pyramid district,
secure it, and use it as a
base from which to operate.
Then we clean the city out,
neighborhood by neighborhood,
street by street,
until the rats
have nowhere left to hide.
I prefer
your earlier suggestion.
Round up the leaders of each of Meereen's
great families and bring them to me.
But I'm the leader of my family.
No, Your Grace.
I had nothing to do with this.
Your Grace!
( speaking Valyrian )
Don't want to overfeed them.
Tomorrow perhaps.
( men whimpering )
( roaring )
"And though Daenerys maintains
her grip on Slaver's Bay,"
forces rise against her
from within and without.
She refuses to leave
until the freedom
"of the former slaves is secure."
She sounds like quite a woman.
And she's alone,
under siege,
no family to guide her
or protect her.
Her last relation
thousands of miles away,
useless, dying.
Don't say that, Maester Aemon.
A Targaryen alone in the world
is a terrible thing.
Maester Aemon.
Lord Commander.
Sam, I'd like to speak
to the maester alone.
How are you feeling?
Oh, like a hundred-year-old man
slowly freezing to death.
I need your advice.
There's something I want
to do, something I...
have to do.
But it'll divide
the Night's Watch.
Bitterly.
Half the men will hate me the
moment I give the order.
Half the men hate you
already, Lord Commander.
Do it.
But you don't know what it is.
That doesn't matter.
You do.
You will find little joy
in your command.
But with luck,
you will find the strength
to do what needs to be done.
Kill the boy, Jon Snow.
Winter is almost upon us.
Kill the boy
and let the man be born.
Where are the rest
of the free folk now?
Where have they gone?
Who leads them?
They followed Mance.
They won't follow anyone else.
What about you?
Hard to lead
when you're in chains.
What if I unchained you?
Why would you do that?
Because you are not my enemy.
And I'm not yours.
You sure seemed like my enemy
when you were killing my friends.
For 8,000 years the Night's
Watch have sworn an oath
to be the shield that
guards the realms of men.
And for 8,000 years we've
fallen short of that oath.
You belong to the realms of men.
All of you.
And now everything
is going to change?
- It is.
- Why now?
Because now I am Lord Commander
of the Night's Watch.
What would you have me do,
Lord Commander?
I'd have you go
north of the Wall.
Gather the remaining free folk wherever
they are and bring them back here.
I'll open the gates for
them and let them through.
I'll find them lands to
settle south of the Wall.
They won't kneel for you
and neither will I.
I don't want them
to kneel for me.
I want them to fight with
me when the time comes.
The day I ask my people
to fight with the crows
is the day my people
cut my guts from my belly
and make me eat them.
And how many of your
people can't fight?
The women, the children,
the old, the sick...
What happens to them?
You're condemning them to death.
Worse than death because you're
too proud to make peace.
Or maybe you're not proud.
Maybe you're just a coward.
Easy thing to say
to a man in chains.
Your people need a leader.
And they need to get south of
the Wall before it's too late.
We don't have much time
and they have less.
The walkers are coming and
they'll hit your people first.
I'm not asking you to make
peace to save your skin.
Make peace to save your people.
Most of them are at Hardhome.
You know where that is?
Up on Storrold's Point.
I can give you 10 horses
and nine other men.
You can get there in a week.
We'll need ships.
I'll talk to King Stannis
about lending you his fleet.
All right, then.
You're coming with me.
You're the Lord Commander
of the Night's Watch.
They need to hear it from you.
They need to know
the ships they are boarding
won't be torched
in the middle of the sea.
You come with me or I don't go.
( Men shouting )
( shouting continues )
You'd bring wildlings here
through our gates?
Men, women, and children will die
by the thousands if we do nothing.
Let them die. We got our
own to worry about.
- Less enemies for us.
- ( cheering )
Fewer.
- What?
- Nothing.
Look, well, there is
good farmland in the Gift.
- ( Men laughing )
- Land that no one uses now.
A dozen abandoned villages.
And why do you think the farmers
abandoned those villages?
Because the wildlings
raided them for years.
Cut them down just like
they did this boy's people.
Men: Aye!
Alliser: We've been fighting
them for thousands of years.
They've slaughtered villages.
They've slaughtered
our brothers.
And we've slaughtered theirs.
I will follow you
anywhere, you know that.
- But they killed Grenn.
- Men: Yes.
- And they killed Pyp.
- Men: Aye.
They killed 50 of our brothers.
I can't forget that.
I can't forgive it.
You were at the Fist
of the First Men.
If we abandon them,
you know what they become.
We can learn to live
with the wildlings
or we can add them
to the army of the dead.
Whatever they are now,
they're better than that.
( All arguing )
( pounding at door )
Thank you.
Olly.
If you have something
you want to say to me,
say it.
It's all right.
You don't mean it, do you?
Telling the wildlings
you want to make peace.
You're just doing it
to trick them.
It's not a trick.
They burned my village.
They put an arrow
through my father's head
right in front of me.
They butchered my mother,
everyone I ever knew.
I know what it's like
to lose the people you love.
I know this is hard for you.
But winter is coming.
We know what's coming with it.
We can't face it alone.
Will there be anything else
you need, Lord Commander?
No.
( Sighs )
- ( horse neighs )
-  ( people chatting )
( bird screeching )
( door opens )
( door closes )
She's far away
from the Lannisters.
This is her home.
Maybe Lady Sansa's
better off here.
Better off with the Boltons
who murdered
her mother and brother?
Sansa's in danger even
if she doesn't realize it.
( Door opens )
Thank you.
You've lived here a long time?
Aye.
Did you know Lord Eddard?
I knew him
and his father before him.
The Starks are gone now.
Not all of them.
I know who's inside that castle.
Everyone knows.
The Boltons.
I'm not talking
about the Boltons.
I need to get a message to her.
To Sansa Stark.
Who are you?
Someone who swore
to keep her safe.
Swore to who?
Her mother.
Her mother's dead.
That doesn't release me
from an oath.
I served Lady Catelyn.
I serve her still.
Who do you serve?
Ramsay: Come back here.
Myranda.
I saw you staring at her.
I'm going to marry her.
That will involve looking
at her from time to time.
You said you'd marry me.
And I meant it.
When I was a bastard named Snow.
But I'm a Bolton now.
What I want is no longer
the primary consideration.
I'm furthering a dynasty.
Do you think she's pretty?
( Scoffs ) Of course I do.
I'm not blind.
( Sighs )
You think she's pretty, too.
I'm looking forward
to our wedding night.
But don't worry, I'll have
plenty of time for you.
Perhaps I'll marry, too.
( laughs )
You're the kennel
master's daughter.
Who are you going to marry,
the stable keeper's son?
You're mine.
You're not going anywhere.
Unless I have to listen
to more of your jealousy.
Jealousy bores me. You remember
what happens to people who bore me.
You're not going to bore
me, are you, Myranda?
Never.
( Knocking on door )
Beg pardon, my lady.
I've come to refill
the wash basin.
Oh, I don't need...
You still have
friends in the North.
If you're ever in trouble,
light a candle in the highest
window of the broken tower.
- But who...
- You're not alone.
I like your dress.
Who made it for you?
I made it myself.
Really?
Who... who are you?
I'm Myranda, the kennel
master's daughter.
May I?
Oh, wonderful.
The stitching.
- Who taught you?
- My mother.
I'm sorry for what
happened to her.
Thank you.
It's good that she taught you.
It was a gift.
Now every time you wear
something you made,
you can remember her.
I'd rather have a mother.
I know. It's not the same.
Still, it's good to remember.
Remember the way things were.
I almost forgot.
There's something else
to help you remember.
( dogs barking )
Down there at the end.
What is it?
That would spoil the surprise.
( Dogs growling )
Go ahead, it's perfectly safe.
You won't believe it
when you see it.
( Growling continues )
( dogs barking )
- ( barking continues )
- ( chains rattling )
Theon?
You shouldn't be here.
( Wind whistling )
You smell particularly
ripe this evening.
Pour me some wine.
Do you have
something to tell me?
No, my lord.
Reek.
She saw me.
Who?
Sansa. Lady Sansa.
She came to the kennels.
She saw you?
Yes. I'm sorry, master.
Forgive me. I didn't think...
Come here.
You mustn't keep
secrets from me, Reek.
Get on your knees.
Give me your hand.
I forgive you.
I trust you find your
chamber suitable, my lady.
Yes, thank you, my lord.
Allow me.
Mother.
Thank you, Ramsay.
My lady, we are all a
family, we northerners.
Our blood ties go back
thousands of years.
So I'd like to drink
to our wedding.
May our happiness
spread from Moat Cailin
to the Last Hearth.
To your wedding.
It must be difficult for you
being in a strange place.
This isn't a strange place.
This is my home.
It's the people who are strange.
You're right.
Very strange.
More wine, please.
Ramsay: I heard you two
had been reunited.
A fitting place for it.
I like to imagine that
the last time you spoke
was in this very room.
Are you still angry with him
after he...
what he did?
Don't worry.
The North remembers.
I punished him for it.
He's not ironborn anymore.
Not Theon Greyjoy anymore.
He's a new man.
A new person, anyway.
Aren't you, Reek?
Yes, master.
That's his new name... Reek.
Why are you doing this?
Because Reek has
something to say to you.
Don't you, Reek?
An apology.
Apologize to Lady Sansa
for what you did.
Apologize for murdering
her two brothers.
I'm sorry.
Look at her, Reek.
An apology doesn't mean anything
if you're not looking
the person in the eye.
- I'm sorry.
- Ramsay: Sorry about what?
For killing your brothers.
There, over and done with.
Doesn't everyone
feel better? I do.
That was getting very tense.
Whew.
You know what, my lady?
What with him having
murdered your brothers
and the rest
of your family gone...
Reek here is the nearest
thing to living kin
that you have left.
Reek.
You will give away the bride.
Someone has to.
What better person?
Good? Good?
Yes, yes, very good.
Wonderful.
Walda and I have
some good news as well,
since we're all together.
We're going to have a baby.
I'm very happy for you.
From the way she's carrying,
Maester Wolkan says
it looks like a boy.
Ramsay: How can you be sure?
Sure of what?
That she's pregnant.
I mean...
how can you tell?
Maester Wolkan has assured
us beyond all doubt.
So how did you manage it?
Manage what?
Getting her pregnant.
I imagine you're familiar
with the procedure.
Of course, but how did you...
find it?
You disgraced yourself at dinner
parading that creature
before the Stark girl.
- And if it's a boy?
- ( chuckles )
You're worried about
your position.
My position is quite clear.
I'm your son
until a better
alternative comes along.
You've never asked me
about your mother.
Why would I?
She had me, she died.
And here we are.
She was a peasant girl.
Pretty in a common sort of way.
She was the miller's wife.
Apparently they had married
without my knowledge or consent.
So I had him hanged
and I took her beneath the
tree where he was swaying.
She fought me the whole time.
She was lucky
I didn't hang her, too.
A year later
she came to my gates
with a squalling baby
in her arms.
A baby she claimed was mine.
I nearly had her whipped
and the child
thrown in the river.
But then I looked at you
and I saw then what I see now.
You are my son.
Stannis Baratheon has
an army at Castle Black.
But he won't stay for long.
He wants the Iron Throne,
and the road to King's Landing
comes right through Winterfell.
He means to take the North.
But the North is ours.
It's yours and mine.
Will you help me defeat him?
Yes.
Is this every book there is?
Every book there is?
- In the world.
- Well, no.
There are thousands and
thousands of books out there.
This library is rather
small, actually.
Where you grew up,
were there more books?
My father's not
the most literate man.
They say the Citadel has the
largest library in the world.
Where's that?
The Citadel?
In Oldtown.
I'm sorry I don't know things.
Oh, Gilly, look at me.
You know how to do a hundred
things I can never do.
You can build a fire
with wet wood.
You can cook.
You can stitch a wound.
I can wash the linens.
I can sweep the floor.
- Well...
- Why does the Citadel have the biggest library?
It's where they train
the maesters.
Like Maester Aemon?
I wanted to be one
when I was young.
Instead, I became a man
of the Night's Watch.
Far more adventure
up here anyway.
I wouldn't have met you.
( Footsteps )
Ah, Your Grace.
You're Samwell Tarly?
I am, Your Grace.
Your father is Randyll Tarly.
He defeated my brother
at the Battle of Ashford.
Only battle Robert ever lost.
I told him he shouldn't go so far
west so soon, but he never listened.
Fine soldier, your father.
You don't look like a soldier.
But I'm told you killed
a white walker.
I did, Your Grace.
How?
With a dagger
made of dragonglass.
Dragonglass?
What the maesters call obsidian.
I know what it is.
We have it in Dragonstone.
Why would obsidian
kill a walker?
I don't know.
I've been going through
all the old manuscripts
hoping to find something,
and all I've learned
is that the children of the forest
used to hunt with dragonglass.
The Lady Melisandre told me
that death marches on the Wall.
I've seen it, Your Grace.
Seen what?
The army of the dead.
- And when they come...
- We have to know how to fight them.
Keep reading, Samwell Tarly.
It's time.
Uh, Your Grace.
Wouldn't it be better to wait?
When Jon Snow returns with the wildlings,
we could have thousands more men.
If Jon Snow returns
with the wildlings.
We can't wait that long.
We have the advantage... more men,
more horses, all fed and rested.
But every day we wait, the
odds shift in Bolton's favor.
This could turn to winter
at any moment.
We have to act now.
Give the order.
We march at sunrise.
I'll choose a dozen men to stay
and guard the queen
and the princess.
No need. They're coming with us.
It's a tough road ahead,
Your Grace.
- Won't they be safer...
- Here?
Half these watchmen
are killers and rapists.
No, they march with us.
As you wish, Your Grace.
( Wind howling )
- ( chatter )
- ( horses snorting )
Shireen: Do you think Father will
let me go down into the crypt?
Davos: Beg your pardon?
At Winterfell.
All the Kings in the North
are buried there.
Bran the Builder
and King Dorren and...
First things first.
It's a long march ahead.
And then we have
to take the castle.
Is there going to be a battle?
Aye, princess, but you
won't be anywhere near...
That's enough talk
of battle, Ser Davos.
You'll scare the child.
Davos: Yes, my queen.
- I'm not scared.
- Well, I am.
When the battle comes,
promise you'll protect me.
I promise.
I hope you know what you're
doing with these wildlings.
I need those ships.
You'll get them back,
I swear it.
Have a safe journey, Your Grace.
And thank you.
Man: Mount up!
Colors!
( horses neighing )
( groans )
No.
You're still too weak.
( Speaking Valyrian )
Ser Barristan?
Are you ashamed?
You were ambushed, outnumbered.
There was no way
you could have known.
This is not why.
Wounded in war,
there is no shame for this.
I am ashamed
because when the knife go in
and I fall to the ground,
I am afraid.
All men fear death.
No, not death.
I fear
I never again see Missandei
from the Island of Naath.
Now you have given the
Masters what they deserve.
If I give everyone
what they deserve,
I'll have no one left to rule.
Ser Barristan counseled mercy
when I took this city right
up to the morning he died.
Daario Naharis thinks I should
kill the former Masters
and let the rest of the
city fend for itself.
What do you think?
Your Grace, I think
that I am not fit
to have an opinion
on these matters.
You are as fit as anyone I know.
You know why I'm here.
And you know who will suffer the
most if this all falls apart.
So what do you think?
I can only tell you
what I have seen, Your Grace.
I have seen you listen
to your counselors.
I have seen you lean on their
experience when your own was lacking
and weigh the choices
they put before you.
And I have seen you
ignore your counselors...
because there was
a better choice.
One that only you could see.
My... my queen,
please do not do this.
What about "valar morghulis"?
I did not want to die a coward.
Apparently I do not
want to die at all.
( Sniffles )
It takes courage to admit fear.
And to admit a mistake.
I came here to tell you
that I was wrong.
I was wrong and you were right.
About tradition.
About bringing the people
of this city together.
I will reopen the fighting pits.
To free men only.
Slavery will never return to
Meereen, not while I live.
Yes, my queen.
And in order to forge a lasting
bond with the Meereenese people,
I will marry the leader
of an ancient family.
Thankfully a suitor
is already on his knees.
Don't worry.
I'll be fine. Nothing
broken, I don't think.
Where are we now?
Not the Rhoyne.
Long, sullen silences
and an occasional
punch in the face.
The Mormont way.
Let's start over.
I apologize for before.
My mouth sometimes
runs away from me.
This doesn't have to be
an unpleasant trip.
We're going to be spending a lot of
time together on the way to Meereen.
We are.
What would make our time
together truly enjoyable
would be some wine.
No wine.
I am a person who drinks.
People who drink
need to keep drinking.
Otherwise, they're not...
I know where we are.
You're taking us
through Valyria.
I am.
Have you sailed
this route before?
No.
You're going to bring
Daenerys a souvenir
from her ancestral homeland
in case I'm not enough?
I think you'll be plenty.
You know what they say.
The Doom still rules Valyria.
What about the demons
and the flames?
Aren't you afraid of the Doom?
Jorah: No.
But pirates are.
Oh.
Tyrion: The Smoking Sea.
How many centuries
before we learn
how to build cities
like this again?
For thousands of years
the Valyrians were
the best in the world
at almost everything.
And then...
And then they weren't.
"They held each other close and
turned their backs upon the end."
The hills that split asunder
and the black
that ate the skies;
The flames that shot
so high and hot
that even dragons burned;
Would never be the final sights
that fell upon their eyes.
A fly upon a wall,
"the waves the sea wind
whipped and churned..."
"The city of a thousand years,"
and all that men had learned;
The Doom consumed it all alike,
"and neither of them turned."
I would clap.
I suppose this is it, then.
This is what remains.
( Water splashes )
What was that?
- ( Rasping )
- Stone Men!
Don't let them touch you!
Get behind!
Mormont, cut me free!
Mormont!
- Mormont!
- ( shouts )
( faintly ) Tyrion?
Tyrion.
You're all right.
You're heavier than you look.
Did any of them touch you?
You?
I've seen greyscale before,
but nothing like that.
I suppose that's why
they send them there.
It'd be kinder to put daggers in
their hearts and be done with it.
Thank you for saving me.
Of course, I wouldn't
have needed saving
if you hadn't kidnapped me
in the first place.
So what now?
We walk up the coast.
With luck, we'll find
a fishing village.
Maybe another boat.
Without luck?
We've got a long walk
ahead of us.
I'll get some wood for a fire.
Try to get some rest, huh?
That's the best idea
you've had all day.
MovieFull-HD.com
by PertamaX